Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Editorial Files, 1944-2016; 3
  - Feldman, Ilana and Ticktin, Miriam: In the Name of Humanity, 2007-2010 (Box 229)
  - Feldman, Lawrence: Lost Shores, Forgotten Peoples, 1997-2001 (Box 158)
  - Felleza, Kevin: Birds of Fire, 2005-2011 (Box 244)
  - Fenella Cannell, 2003-2006 (Box 282)
  - Ferguson, 1992 (Box 340)
  - Ferguson, Arthur: Utter Antiquity, 1990-1993 (Box 199)
  - Ferguson, James Gupta, Akhil: Culture Power Place, 1995-1997 (Box 169)
  - Ferguson, James: Give a Man a Fish: Reflections on the New Politics of Distribution, 2014-2015 (Box 359)
  - Ferguson, Kennan: All in the Family, 2008-2011 (Box 251)
  - Fernandes, 2008-2010 (Box 325)
  - Fernandez, Hector; Cumbia!, 2012 (Box 110)
  - Fernandez, Hector; Cumbia!; Permissions, 2012 (Box 110)
  - Fernando, Mayanthi, 2012-2014 (Box 90)
  - Ferraro, Thomas: Catholic Lives, 1993-1997 (Box 169)
  - Ferre, 1989-1993 (Box 340)
  - Fetter, 1977-1983 (Box 340)
  - Feuer, Jane: Seeing Through the Eighties, 1992-1996 (Box 199)
  - Feuer, Jane: TV and the New Right, 1989 (Box 320)
    Proposal and correspondence
  - Few, Martha and Tortorici, Zec, eds.; Centering Animals in Latin American History, 2010-2012 (Box 110)
  - Fiction in Translation, 1988-1991 (Box 320)
  - Field, Allyson: Uplift Cinema: The Emergence of African American Film and the Possiblity of Black Modernity, 2013-2015 (Box 359)
  - Field, Les: The Grimace of Macho Raton, 1995-1998 (Box 169)
  - Fields (Box 299)
  - Fierman, William: Soviet Central Asia, 1985-1989 (Box 199)
  - Figal, Gerald: Civilization and Monsters, 1997-2000 (Box 153)
  - Findlay, Eileen J.; Bregano the Beet Fields, Dreaming of Domesticity, 2013 (Box 90)
  - Findlay, Eileen: Imposing Decency, 1996-2000 (Box 170)
  - Findlay; Permissions, 2013 (Box 90)
  - Findlay; We are Left Without a Father Here, 2013 (Box 90)
  - Finke, Michael: Metapoeisis, 1992-1995 (Box 199)
  - Finkelpearl, Tom; What We Made, 2010-2013 (Box 110)
  - Finnston, 2006-2007 (Box 291)
  - Finnstrom, Sverker; Virtual War and Magical Death, 2010-2012 (Box 116)
  - Finucci, Valeria, 1999-2000 (Box 265)
  - Finucci, Valeria and Brownlee, Kevin: Generation and Degeneration, 1997-2001 (Box 217)
  - Finucci, Valeria: Renaissance Transactions, 1997-1998 (Box 170)
  - Fischer, Brodwyn; Cities from Scratch, 2011-2013 (Box 119)
  - Fischer, Brodwyn; Cities from Scratch; Permissions, 2013 (Box 119)
  - Fischer, Frank: Citizens, Experts, and Environment, 1997-2000 (Box 170)
  - Fischer, Frank; The Argumentative Turn Revisited, 2010-2011 (Box 101)
  - Fischer, Michael M.J. Persian Media, 2003-2005 (Box 269)
    Mute Dreams, Blind Owls, and Dispersed Knowledges and Emergent Forms of Life and the Anthropological Voice
  - Fischer, Michael: Anthropological Futures, 2007-2009 (Box 306)
  - Fischer, Sibylle; Modernity Disavowed, 2002-2004 (Box 96)
  - Fischer, Sibylle; Modernity Disavowed; Contract, 2002-2005 (Box 96)
  - Fischlin, Daniel; The Fierce Urgency, 2012-2013 (Box 111)
  - Fiscus, Ronald: The Constitutional Logic of Affirmative Action, 1995 (Box 142)
  - Fish People, 1987 April 15-1992 March 11 (Box 295)
    Correspondence, primarily with Stanley Fish and individuals recommended by Fish to DUP
  - Fish, Stanley: Doing What Comes Naturally, 1988-1990 (Box 170)
  - Fish, Stanley: Doing What Comes Naturally, 1984-1990 (Box 170)
  - Fish, Stanley: Doing What Comes Naturally, 1988-1991 (Box 170)
  - Fisher Melissa, 2003-2006 (Box 277)
  - Fisher, Gary: Gary in Your Pocket, 1995-1996 (Box 144)
  - Fisher, Melissa; Art and Permissions, 2011-2012 (Box 101)
  - Fisher, Melissa; Contract, 2011 (Box 101)
  - Fisher, Melissa; Wall Street Women, 2010-2012 (Box 101)
  - Fitting, Elizabeth: The Struggle for Maize, 2009-2011 (Box 238)
  - Fitting, Elizabeth: The Struggle for Maize, 2007-2009 (Box 238)
  - Fitzlyon, Kyril: The Memoirs of Princess Dashkova, 1993-1995 (Box 198)
  - Flaumenhaft, Harvey: The Effective Republic, 1990-1992 (Box 199)
  - Fletcher, Robert; Romancing the Wild, 2012-2013 (Box 119)
  - Fletcher, Robert; Romancing the Wild; Permissions, 2013 (Box 119)
  - Flores, 1991-1993 (Box 340)
  - Flores, Juan and Miriam Jimenez Roman, 2007-2011 (Box 93)
  - Florida, Nancy: Writing the Past, Inscribing the Future, 1994-1997 (Box 200)
  - Fodor Eva, 2001 (Box 265)
  - Fog Olwig, 2004-2009 (Box 289)
  - Foley, Barbara: Radical Representations, 1992-1993 (Box 200)
  - Foley, Barbara: Wrestling with the Left, 2007-2011 (Box 230)
  - Foner, Eric, 1989 February 6 (Box 320)
  - Forester, John Fischer, Frank: The Argumentative Turn in Policy Analysis and Planning, 1987-1992 (Box 200)
  - Forman, Murray; One Night on TV is Worth Weeks at the Paramount, 2002-2012 (Box 101)
  - Forrest, Alan: Soldiers of the French Revolution, 1985-1990 (Box 200)
  - Foster, Anne: Projections of Power, 2004-2009 (Box 230)
  - Fouron, Georges Schiller, Nina: Georges Woke Up Laughing, 1999-2001 (Box 172)
  - Fourth World Congress for Soviet and East European Studies, 1989 February 1-1990 July 26 (Box 320)
  - Fowle, 1998 (Box 348)
  - Fowlie, Wallace: Journal of Rehearsals, 1976-1996 (Box 200)
  - Fowlie, Wallace: Memory, 1988-1990 (Box 200)
  - Fowlie, Wallace: Rimbaud and Jim Morrison, 1999-1992 (Box 170)
  - Fox, Pamela: Hidden Resistances, 1992-1996 (Box 200)
  - Fradkin: Verbal Categories and the Linguistic Sign, 1988 September 12-13 (Box 320)
  - Franco, Jean: Critical Passions, 1995-2000 (Box 170)
  - Franco, Jean; Cruel Modernity, 2011-2014 (Box 111)
  - Francoise Verges, 1996-1998 (Box 301)
  - Frank & Andrew Dubois (Box 269)
  - Frank, Richard: Al-Ghazali and the Asharite School, 1992-1994 (Box 200)
  - Frankenberg, Ruth: Displacing Whiteness, 1993-1999 (Box 170)
  - Frankenberg, Ruth: Displacing Whiteness, 1997-1999 (Box 170)
  - Frankenburg: Dis/Placing Whiteness Ads and Reviews, 1996-1999 (Box 344)
  - Frankerberg, 1997--1999 (Box 349)
  - Franklin, 1997-2003 (Box 350)
  - Franklin, John: George Washington Williams, 1997-1998 (Box 170)
  - Franklin, Sarah: Relative Values, 1999-2002 (Box 219)
  - Franklin, Sarah; Dolly Mixtures, 2009-2013 (Box 113)
  - Franzen and Borinsky: Mean Broad, 1990 (Box 320)
    Correspondence, reader reports, and excerpts
  - Frazier, 2003-2007 (Box 278)
  - Frazier, Danny Wilcox, 2006-2007 (Box 262)
  - Frazier, Robeson: The East Is Black: Cold War China in the Black Radical Imagination, 2012-2015 (Box 359)
  - Fred Roser, 2005-2007 (Box 297)
  - Fred Wesley, 1998-2002 (Box 511)
  - Frederick Moehn, 2004-2011 (Box 93)
  - Freedman, 1982-1991 (Box 321)
  - Freeman, Carla, 2004-2014 (Box 90)
  - Freeman, Carla: High Tech and High Heels, 1994-2001 (Box 171)
  - Freeman, Elizabeth: Time Binds, 2008-2011 (Box 230)
  - Fregoso Rosa, 2007-2011 (Box 309)
  - French & James, 1998 (Box 349)
  - French and James: Gendered Worlds of..., 1996-2000 (Box 344)
  - French and James: Review Slip F97, 1997 (Box 344)
    Review slip for The Gendered Worlds of Latin American Women Workers
  - French Publisher Contract; Librairie Artheme Fayard (Publisher)- Sapiro, 2009 (Box 93)
  - French, John James, Daniel: The Gendered Worlds of Latin America Woman Workers, 1994-1997 (Box 132)
  - French, John James, Daniel: The Gendered Worlds of Latin America Woman Workers, 1997 (Box 132)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1996-1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1996-1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1996-1998 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1995-1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1996-1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1995-1996 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1996 (Box 142)
  - Friedberg, Ruth: Art Song in America, 1995-1997 (Box 142)
  - Friedrich Carl, 1980-1986 (Box 347)
  - Fritz Oehlschlaeger, 1997-2003 (Box 277)
  - Frueh, Joanna, 2005-2006 (Box 262)
  - Frye, David; Narrative Transculturation in Latin America, 2000-2011 (Box 102)
  - Fubini, Riccardo: Humanism and Secularization, 1991-2003 (Box 171)
  - Fuchs, Daniel: The Limits of Ferocity, 2008-2011 (Box 238)
  - Fuente, Ariel de la: Children of Facundo, 1998-2000 (Box 167)
  - Fujii Jim, 1997-2003 (Box 305)
  - Fujitani, T.: Perilous Memories, 1994-2001 (Box 158)
  - Fuqua, Joy V.; Ill Effects, 2002-2011 (Box 104)
  - Furst, Lillian: All is True, 1993-1996 (Box 200)
  - Furtado (Box 346)
  - Furuhata, Yuriko; Cinema of Actuality, 2010-2013 (Box 113)
  - Fuss, Diana; Dying Modern, 2010-2013 (Box 111)
  - Gabara, 2003-2007 (Box 299)
  - Gabbard, Krin: Representing Jazz, 1992-1999 (Box 200)
  - Gabriel Rockhill, 2005-2011 (Box 326)
  - Gabriella, 1999-2001 (Box 265)
  - Gado, Frank: The Passion of Ingmar Bergman, 1983-1996 (Box 200)
  - Gado, Frank: The Passion of Ingmar Berman, 1986-1989 (Box 307)
  - Gaines, Jane: Classical Hollywood Narrative, 1989-1992 (Box 200)
  - Galli, Carlo, edited by Adam Sitze, translated by Amanda Minervini: Janus' Gaze, 2009-2015 (Box 365)
  - Gallichio, Marc, 2005-2007 (Box 258)
  - Gallop, 1997-2003 (Box 265)
  - Gallop, Jane, 2000-2001 (Box 265)
  - Gallop, Jane: Feminist Accused of Sexual Harassment, 1995-1999 (Box 171)
  - Gallop, Jane: The Deaths of the Author, 2008-2011 (Box 244)
  - Gandhi, 2004-2005 (Box 267)
  - Ganti, Tejaswini: Producing Bollywood, 2001-2012 (Box 251)
  - Gaonkar, Dilip: Alternative Modernities, 1999-1001 (Box 217)
  - Garces, Jean, 1990 (Box 320)
  - Garcia, Cindy; Salsa Crossings, 2010-2012 (Box 113)
  - Gardaphe, Fred: Italian Signs, American Streets, 1994-1998 (Box 171)
  - Gardell, Mattias: Countdown to Armageddon, 1995-1999 (Box 139)
  - Gardield, Seth: Indigenous Struggle at the Heart of Brazil, 1996-2001 (Box 172)
  - Garfield, Seth; In Search of the Amazon, 2011-2012 (Box 113)
  - Garfield, Seth; In Search of the Amazon; Permissions, 2012 (Box 113)
  - Garner: The Absent Voice: Narrative Comprehension in the Theater, 1987-1988 (Box 320)
    Correspondence and internal records
  - Garroway, 2000-2003 (Box 512)
  - Gaskin, Gerard H.; Legendary, 2012-2013 (Box 116)
  - Gasper, David Berry; Bondsmen and Rebels, 1992-1993 (Box 95)
  - Gavilan Sanchez, Lurgio: When Rains Became Floods: A Child Soldier's Story, 2013-2014 (Box 359)
  - Gavin, 2002-2006 (Box 259)
  - Gayatri, 2002-2003 (Box 512)
  - Gedicks, Frederick: The Rhetoric of Church and State, 1994-1995 (Box 201)
  - Geismar, Haidy; Treasured Possessions, 2010-2015 (Box 111)
  - Gelfant, Blanche: Views of Their Own, 1992-1994 (Box 201)
  - Gellman, Peter: MS on Lester B. Pearson, 1989 (Box 320)
  - Gellner, David; Borderlands of Northern South Asia, 2010-2012 (Box 119)
  - General Correspondense, 2004-2007 (Box 316)
  - Gender Relations in German History, 1997 (Box 343)
  - Geogre Marcus/ Paul Rainbow/ James Fabian, 2007-2010 (Box 297)
  - George Harris, 1990 (Box 336)
  - George Hartley, 1997-2003 (Box 263)
  - George Marcus, 1991-2000 (Box 301)
  - George Yudice, 1993-2002 (Box 274)
  - Georgina Black, 1995-2005 (Box 305)
  - Gerald, 1988 (Box 329)
  - Gerassi-Navarro, Nina: Pirate Novels, 1994-2000 (Box 154)
  - Gerd, 2004-2007 (Box 279)
  - Gerhardt, Michael: The Federal Appointments Process, 1998-2002 (Box 159)
  - Gerson, Judith, 2002-2007 (Box 279)
  - Gerstener (Box 267)
  - Ghodsee, Kristen: Lost in Translation, 2009-2011 (Box 244)
  - Ghodsee, Kristen: The Left Side of History: World War II and the Unfulfilled Promise of Communism in Eastern Europe, 2013-2015 (Box 359)
  - Ghosh, Bishnupriya: Global Icons, 2007-2011 (Box 244)
  - Gietman, Matthew, 2000-2003 (Box 263)
  - Giles, Paul: Virtual Americas, 2000-2002 (Box 172)
  - Gill Lesley, 2002-2004 (Box 268)
  - Gilleroy, John Martin: The Moral Poverty of Environmental Decisionmaking, 2000-2001 (Box 307)
  - Gillette, Phillip and Frank Willard: Tethered Navy, 1987-1988 (Box 320)
  - Gilliam, Bryan: Richard Strauss, 1996-1997 (Box 146)
  - Gilliam, Bryan: Richard Strauss, 1991-1993 (Box 201)
  - Gillingham, Paul and Smith, Ben; La Dictablanda, 2010-2012 (Box 119)
  - Gillingham, Paul and Smith, Ben; La Dictablanda; Permissions, 2010-2013 (Box 119)
  - Gillis MALCOM, 1987-1990 (Box 287)
  - Gillman, Howard, 1992-1993 (Box 96)
  - Gillman, Howard; The Constitution Besieged, 1992 (Box 95)
  - Gillman, Susan Robinson, Forrest: Mark Twains Puddnhead Wilson, 1988-1991 (Box 201)
  - Gillroy, John and Bowersox, Joe: The Moral Austerity of Environmental Decision-making, 2000-2002 (Box 223)
  - Gilman, 1997-2002 (Box 353)
  - Gilman, Sander: Creating Beauty to Cure the Soul, 1997-1998 (Box 148)
  - Gilmore, Paul: The Genuine Article, 1998-2001 (Box 219)
  - Ginsberg, Elaine: Passing and the Fictions of Identity, 1993-1998 (Box 201)
  - Gitelman, Lisa; Paper Knowledge, 2010-2014 (Box 119)
  - Glave, Thomas, editor; Our Caribbean..; Permissions, 2005-2008 (Box 96)
  - Glazener, 1999 (Box 348)
  - Glazener, Nancy: Reading for Realism, 1995-1997 (Box 171)
  - Gleckner, Robert Pfau, Thomas: Lessons of Romanticism, 1996-1999 (Box 172)
  - Gledhill, John: New Approaches to Resistance in Brazil and Mexico, 2008-2012 (Box 251)
  - Gless, Darryl Smith, Barbara: The Politics of Liberal Education, 1991-1992 (Box 201)
  - Gless, Darryl Smith, Barbara: The Politics of Liberal Education, 1992-1995 (Box 201)
  - Glover, David: Vampires, Mummies and Liberals, 1995-1996 (Box 171)
  - Gluch, Carol and Anna Lowenhaupt Tsing, eds.; Words in Motion, 2008-2009 (Box 96)
  - Glynn, Kevin: Tabloid Culture, 1995-2001 (Box 172)
  - Go Julian & Anne Foster (Box 263)
  - Gogol, Miriam: Theodore Drieser: Beyond Naturalism, 1994 (Box 320)
  - Gold, Ann: In the Time of Trees and Sorrows, 2000-2002 (Box 223)
  - Gold, Hazel: The Reframing of Realism, 1991-1993 (Box 201)
  - Goldberg, Jonathan: Queering the Renaissance, 1992-1994 (Box 172)
  - Goldberg, Jonathan: Willa Cather and Others, 1999-2001 (Box 217)
  - Goldstein, Alyosha, 2012-2014 (Box 90)
  - Goldstein, Alyosha, editor; Art and Permissions, 2014 (Box 90)
  - Goldstein, Alyosha: Poverty in Common, 2006-2011 (Box 251)
  - Goldstein, Daniel, 2002-2003 (Box 268)
  - Goldstein, Daniel; Outlawed, 2011 (Box 104)
  - Goldstein, Daniel; Outlawed; Permissions, 2011 (Box 104)
  - Goldstein; Contract, 2013 (Box 90)
  - Gole, Nilufer: Islam and Secularity, 2013-2015 (Box 365)
  - Golub, Alex; Leviathans at the Gold Mind, 2009-2014 (Box 119)
  - Gomez, Jose Luis, 1988 (Box 320)
    Correspondence and media review
  - Gonzalez, 1996-2000 (Box 352)
  - Gonzalez, Eduardo: The Monstered Self, 1990-1992 (Box 171)
  - Gonzalez, Vernadette Vicuna, 2011-2013 (Box 116)
  - Goodchild, Phillip: Theology of Money, 2007-2008 (Box 306)
    Proposal, reader reports, and correspondence regarding Theology of Money
  - Goodlad, Lauren, and Michael Bibby, eds.; Goth Style, 2007 (Box 95)
  - Goodlad, Lauren; Mad Men, Mad World, 2011-2013 (Box 111)
  - Goodlad, Lauren; Mad Men, Mad World Artwork, 2012 (Box 111)
  - Goodlad, Lauren; Mad Men, Mad World; Contract, 2011-2012 (Box 111)
  - Goodlad, Lauren; Mad Men, Mad World; Final Art, 2013 (Box 111)
  - Goodlad, Lauren; Mad Men, Mad World; Permissions, 2011-2013 (Box 111)
  - Goodwin, 1972-1978 (Box 342)
  - Goodyear-Ka'opua, Hussey, Wright, editors, 2011-2015 (Box 90)
  - Goodyear-Ka'opua, Hussey, Wright, editors; Permissions, 2014 (Box 90)
  - Gootenberg, Paul and Reygadas, Luis: Indelible Inequalities in Latin America, 2006-2009 (Box 230)
  - Gordillo, 2001-2003 (Box 268)
  - Gordillo, Gaston; Sediments of History, 2009-2013 (Box 90)
  - Gordon, 1994 (Box 340)
  - Gorshi, Philip S.; Bourdieu and Historical Analysis, 2007-2012 (Box 104)
  - Gorshi, Philip S.; Bourdieu and Historical Analysis; Contracts, 2011-2012 (Box 104)
  - Gorshi, Philip S.; Bourdieu and Historical Analysis; Final Art and Perms, 2012 (Box 104)
  - Goth Godland, 2002-2007 (Box 279)
  - Gotkowitz, Laura: Indigeneity in the Andes and Mesoamerica, 2008-2011 (Box 251)
  - Gotwitz, Laura Permissions, 2006 (Box 258)
  - Gould Jeffrey, 2006-2007 (Box 291)
  - Gould, Jeffrey: To Die in this Way, 1996-1999 (Box 146)
  - Gow, 2006-2007 (Box 291)
  - Gracyk, Theodore: Rhythm and Noise, 1993-1998 (Box 171)
  - Gracyk, Theodore: Rhythm and Noise, 1993-1994 (Box 171)
  - Graff, Ellen: Stepping Left, 1994-1999 (Box 139)
  - Graham, Julie and Gibson, Katherine: Re/Presenting Class, 1999-2002 (Box 217)
  - Graham, Julie and Gibson, Katherine: Re/Presenting Class, 1998-2000 (Box 217)
  - Grandin, Greg and Joseph, Gilbert: A Century of Revolution, 2003-2010 (Box 230)
  - Grandin, Greg Levenson, Deborah and Oglesby, Elizabeth: The Guatemala Reader, 2000-2011 (Box 245)
  - Grandin, Greg: The Blood of Guatemala, 1998-2001 (Box 172)
  - Grant Hill Art Collection, 2002-2003 (Box 269)
  - Gray, Lila Ellen; Fado Resounding, 2008-2013 (Box 116)
  - Green, 1990 (Box 348)
  - Green, Nancy: Ready-to-Wear and Ready-to-Work, 1992-1997 (Box 172)
  - Green, Ren├⌐e, 2012-2014 (Box 90)
  - Green, Venus: Race on the Line, 1991-2001 (Box 173)
  - Greenhouse, Carol Warren, Kay Mertz, Elizabeth: Ethnography in Unstable Places, 1998-2002 (Box 173)
  - Greening Brazil, 2005 (Box 258)
  - Gregg, Melissa and Seigworth, Gregory: The Affect Theory Reader, 2006-2012 (Box 230)
  - Gretchen Murphy, 2001-2004 (Box 270)
  - Grever, 2000-2003 (Box 269)
  - Grever and Waaldjik: Transforming the Public Sphere: The Dutch National Exhibition of Women's Labor in 1898, 2000-2003 (Box 269)
  - GreWAL, 1997-2003 (Box 512)
  - Grewal, Inderpal: Home and Harem, 1993-1996 (Box 201)
  - Grieshaber, 1988-1991 (Box 334)
  - Grieveson & Wasson, 2002-2010 (Box 296)
  - Gross Kai, 2003-2004 (Box 267)
  - Gross, JoAnn: Identity in the Muslim Societies of Central Asia, 1989-1991 (Box 307)
  - Grossberg (Box 348)
  - Grossburg, Lawrence: Bringing it all Back Home, 1995-1998 (Box 173)
  - Grossburg, Lawrence: Cultural Studies in the Future Tense, 2008-2011 (Box 230)
  - Grossman, 1997-2002 (Box 352)
  - Grossman, Marshall: The Story of All Things, 1995-1998 (Box 139)
  - Grosz Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 268)
  - Grosz, Elizabeth: Becoming Undone, 2009-2011 (Box 244)
  - Grubbs, David; Records Ruin the Landscape, 2010-2014 (Box 119)
  - Grusin, Richard: Reproduction of Nature, 1988-1989 (Box 320)
    Proposal, reader reports, correspondence, and internal records
  - Grusin, Richard: Transcendentalist Hermeneutics, 1988-1990 (Box 201)
  - Gruzinski, Serge: Image at War, 1994-2001 (Box 217)
  - Grzybowski, Kaz, 1989-1990 (Box 320)
  - Guardino, 2003 (Box 512)
  - Gudmundson, Lowell and Wolfe, Justin: Blacks and Blackness in Central America, 2006-2010 (Box 230)
  - Guerin, Daniel: The Brown Plague, 1993-1996 (Box 307)
  - Gugelberger, Georg: The Real Thing, 1994-1996 (Box 133)
  - Gugelberger, Georg: The Real Thing, 1995-1992 (Box 133)
  - Guha, Ranajit: A Rule of Property for Bengal, 1994-1996 (Box 139)
  - Guha, Ranajit: Elementary Aspects of Peasant Insurgency in Colonial India, 1996-2000 (Box 154)
  - Gundle, Stephen: Between Hollywood and Moscow, 1999-2001 (Box 173)
  - Gunlicks: Gorbachev's First Year, 1986 September 12-1988 June 23 (Box 320)
  - Gupta, 1997-1999 (Box 348)
  - Gupta, Akhil: Postcolonial Developments Report, 1996-2000 (Box 173)
  - Guruswamy, 1995-2001 (Box 353)
  - Guruswamy, Lakshman McNeely, Jeffrey: Protection of Global Biodiversity, 1994-1998 (Box 139)
  - Gustafson, Richard: The Imagination of Spring, 1988 (Box 320)
  - Gutierrez Aguilar, Raquel; Los Ritmos del Pachakuti, 2011-2014 (Box 90)
  - Gutierrez-Mouat, Ricardo, 1988 July 6-22 (Box 320)
  - Guy, Donna: Reforming Charity, Creating Rights in Argentina, 2006 May 1-2008 January 29 (Box 306)
    Proposal, reader reports, and correspondence regarding Reforming Charity, Creating Rights in Argentina
  - Gwendolyn Dubois, 2002-2003 (Box 268)
  - Hackney (Box 283)
  - Hadkrishman, 2004-2008 (Box 294)
  - Hahner, June: Emancipating the Female Sex, 1988-1998 (Box 201)
  - Halberstam, 1997-2002 (Box 350)
  - Halberstam, Jack, 1994-1999 (Box 202)
  - Halberstam, Judith: Female Masculinity, 1997-1999 (Box 173)
  - Halberstam, Judith: The Queer Art of Failure, 2008-2011 (Box 245)
  - Haley and Brown: Left Legalism/Left Critique, 1999 September 20-2001 November 15 (Box 510)
  - Hall David, 2004 (Box 512)
  - Hall, David: The Antinomian Controversy, 1636-1638, 1989-1999 (Box 202)
  - Hall, Rachel: The Transparent Traveler, 2012-2015 (Box 365)
  - Hall, Timothy: Contested Boundaries, 1992-1995 (Box 202)
  - Halley & Brown, 1999-2001 (Box 510)
  - Halley, Janet and Parker, Andrew: After Sex?, 2009-2012 (Box 238)
  - Halley, Janet: Don't, 1997-2002 (Box 173)
  - Halliday, Fred: Revolution and World Politics, 1998-2000 (Box 173)
  - Halperin-Donghi, Tulio: The Contemporary History of Latin America, 1986-1999 (Box 173)
  - Halpern, Orit, 2010-2014 (Box 91)
  - Hames-Garcia, Michael and Martinez, Ernesto: Gay Latino Studies, 2008-2010 (Box 238)
  - Hamza, Agon: Repeating Zizek, 2013-2015 (Box 359)
  - Hanafi, Zakiya: The Monster in the Machine, 1994-2002 (Box 159)
  - Hanchard, Michael: Radical Politics in Contemporary Brazil, 1995-1999 (Box 150)
  - Handel, Michael, 1988 (Box 320)
    Correspondence, essays, and art
  - Handler & Grable, 1996-2001 (Box 349)
  - Handler and Gable: Ads and Reviews, 1996-1998 (Box 344)
    Proposal, reviews, correspondence, and marketing materials relating to The New History of an Old Museum
  - Handler and Gable: Review Slip Original, 1997 (Box 344)
  - Handler, Richard Gable, Eric: The New History in an Old Museum, 1994-2000 (Box 173)
  - Handler, Richard Gable, Eric: The New History in an Old Museum, 1996-2001 (Box 173)
  - Hanger, 1991-1997 (Box 348)
  - Hanger, Kimberly: Bounded Lives, Bounded Places, 1991-1999 (Box 143)
  - Hanksy and Friedberg: Review Slip Original, 1997 (Box 344)
    Review slip for Art Song in America\
  - Hansen & Clarke, 2005-2008 (Box 333)
  - Hansen, Julie and Porter, Suzanne: The Physician's Art, 1999-2000 (Box 154)
  - Hansen, Thomas: States of Imagination, 1999-2001 (Box 219)
  - Hansmark, 1987 (Box 330)
  - Hanson, Ellis: Out Takes, 1997-1999 (Box 150)
  - Haralovich, Mary Beth: Television, History, and American Culture, 1997-2002 (Box 154)
  - Harari, Josue: Odeon Series, 1993-1994 (Box 202)
  - Harding, 1998-2006 (Box 275)
  - Harding, 2004-2007 (Box 290)
  - Harding, Neil: Leninism, 1995-1996 (Box 202)
  - Harding, Sandra: The Postcolonial Science and Technology Studies Reader, 2008-2011 (Box 245)
  - Hardt, Michael: The Political Philosophy, 1994-1995 (Box 202)
  - Harlow and Carter; Permissions, 1999-2004 (Box 93)
  - Harney. Stefano. State Work, 1999-2001 (Box 513)
  - Harnhardt, Christina B.; Safe Space, 2010-2013 (Box 117)
  - Harpham, Geoffrey: Shadows of Ethics, 1996-1999 (Box 150)
  - Harriman Institue, 1988 (Box 336)
  - Harris, 1983-1987 (Box 321)
  - Harris, 1985-1987 (Box 346)
  - Harris, Laura Crocker, Elizabeth: Histories, Generations, Futures, 1996-1997 (Box 202)
  - Harris/ Sartor, 2014-2015 (Box 105)
  - Harrison, 1988-1989 (Box 336)
  - Harry West & Todd Sanders, 2002 (Box 269)
  - Hartigan, 1999-2001 (Box 282)
  - Hartley and Schiaffini; File, 2006-2008 (Box 93)
  - Harvey, 1995-2002 (Box 350)
  - Harvey, Neil: The Chiapas Rebellion, 1995-2000 (Box 174)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley: Dispatches From the Front, 1992-1995 (Box 202)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley: The Hauerwas Reader, 1999-2004 (Box 215)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley: The Hauerwas Reader, 1998-2001 (Box 215)
  - Hauerwas, Stanley: The Hauerwas Reader, 1997-1999 (Box 215)
  - Hausman, Bernice: Changing Sex, 1992-1999 (Box 139)
  - Hay, Deborah: Lamb at the Altar, 1992-1993 (Box 307)
  - Hayward, Jack Page, Edward: Governing, 1995 (Box 202)
  - Healey, Mark: The Ruins of the New Argentina, 2006-2010 (Box 238)
  - Health and Hugiene in Chinese East Asia, 2010 (Box 93)
  - Hearn, 2003-2008 (Box 296)
  - Heble, Ajay; The Future of Jazz Is Now!, 2009-2013 (Box 108)